Guide to the Jean Kilbourne Papers, 1918-2014 and undated RL.10982
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Teaching Files, 1969-1993 and undated; 12 boxes
  - Poetry--Rock and other music as poetry, 1969 and undated (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Self, undated (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Vivid images, undated (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Women and feminism, 1971-1975 (Box 64)
  - Prejudice, undated (Box 64)
  - Race--Pamphlets and handouts, 1971-1974 (Box 64)
  - Reading lists, 1960-1974 (Box 64)
  - Science fiction and future studies, 1971-1974 (Box 64)
  - Sexism--Examples, 1966-1995 (Box 64)
  - Sexism--General, 1974-1989 (Box 64)
  - Sexism--Student papers, 1973-1974 (Box 64)
  - Short story articles, 1968-1969 (Box 64)
  - Social dynamics, undated (Box 64)
  - Student papers, 1979-1980 (Box 65)
  - Syllabi and Curricula--Media, 1979-1981 (Box 65)
  - Symbolism and metaphor, 1979 and undated; 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Values, 1973 and undated (Box 65)
  - Values--Articles, 1967-1971 (Box 65)
  - Vietnam protest literature, 1967 and undated (Box 65)
  - Women's Studies, 1972-1977 (Box 65)
  - Writing--Articles and examples, 1976-1977 (Box 65)
- Print Advertisements, 1930-2011 and undated; 1; 22 boxes
  - Alcohol, 1
    - Alcohol, 1981-1996; 5 folders (Box 67)
    - Alcohol, 1987-1999 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol, 1987-2003 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol, 2002-2004 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol, 2004 (Box 67)
    - Absolut Alcohol Ads, 1981-1988 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol 4, 1976-1986 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol 8-78, File-UI, 1987 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol 11, 1986-1996 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol Ads and Sexual Sell: General, 1969-1985 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol Ads: Sex and Romance, 1976-2003 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol Ads-Youth, 1999-2000 (Box 67)
    - Alcohol in Ads for Other Products, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
    - Subliminals: Alcohol, 1973-1984 (Box 67)
    - Absolut Alcohol Ads and Parodies, 1987-1997 (Box 68)
    - Alcohol 5, 1977-1986; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Alcohol 6, 1983-1989 (Box 68)
    - Alcohol 7, 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Alcohol 12, 1980-2002 (Box 68)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1979-2000; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Alcohol, 1981-1984 (Box 68)
    - Alcohol Ads: Sexual Sell Seduction, 1975-1981 (Box 68)
    - Marketing Alcohol, 1976-1981 (Box 68)
    - Sexual Sell: Alcohol as Woman, 1973-1980 (Box 68)
    - Alcohol Ads: An Essential-Daily, All Times and Seasons, Etc., 1977-1979 (Box 69)
    - Adventure with Alcohol, 1978-1980 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol Ads: Life's Ultimate Experience, 1979 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol Ads, Miscellaneous, 1949-1992 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol Ads: Natural, 1978-1980 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol Ads with Minorities, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Addiction, 1988-2003 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Adult Rites, 1977-1988 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Creativity, 1979-1991 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Gourmet Image-Sensual Pleasure, 1977-1979 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Patriotism, 1979-1980 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Promoting Abuse, 1968-1980 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Reward for Success, 1974-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Sexual Sell: Breasts and Babies, 1969-1979 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Sports, 1974-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Travel, 1976-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol and Women, 1958-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol: Freedom and Nonconformity, 1973-1979 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol, History, and Tradition, 1976-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol, Home, and Family, 1979-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol, Love, and Romance, 1975-1988 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol, Machismo, and Power, 1976-1981 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol's Grandiosity, 1977-1979 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol, Sexual Adventure, and Variety, 1977 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol, Wealth, and Sophistication, 1977-1988 (Box 69)
    - Alcohol with Celebrations and Holidays, 1977-1979 (Box 69)
    - Escape with Alcohol, 1948-1981 (Box 69)
    - To shoot-Alcohol, 1973-1991 (Box 69)
  - Alcohol and Cigarette Ads, 2
    - ALC and Rebellion, 1979-1998 (Box 70)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1966-1980 (Box 70)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1979-1981 (Box 70)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1998-2010 (Box 70)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1991-1999 (Box 70)
    - Cig Ads File, 1974-1999 (Box 70)
    - Cigarettes, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Cigarettes, 1990-2004 (Box 70)
    - Cigarettes 1-Ads to File, 1974-1999 (Box 70)
    - Kent and Food, 1980-1982 (Box 70)
    - Newport-Phallic Symbols, 1976-1997 (Box 70)
    - Tobacco Industry Ads-Freedom, 1990-1996 (Box 70)
    - Virginia Slims-Anger/Stress, 1983-1995 (Box 70)
    - Virginia slims-"Woman Thing", 1987-1998 (Box 70)
  - Alcohol, Drugs, and Miscellaneous, 3
    - Alcohol Ads, 1983-2004; 3 folders (Box 71)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1984-2002 (Box 71)
    - Alcohol Ads, 1986-1999 (Box 71)
    - Drugs, 1980-2005 (Box 71)
    - Guess Jeans, 1986-1987 (Box 71)
    - Jeans Ads, 1978-1983 (Box 71)
    - Tobacco Ads, 1930-2010; 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Tobacco Ads, 1974-2003 (Box 71)
  - General Ads, 4
    - Anorexia/Eating Disorders, 1982-1984 (Box 72)
    - Car Ads, 1994-1998 (Box 72)
    - Cars, 1998-2002 (Box 72)
    - Cars and Food, 1996-1997 (Box 72)
    - Diet, 1982-1999 (Box 72)
    - Food and Diet Ads, 1987-2003; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Food and Diet Ads, 1996-2010 (Box 72)
    - Food and Dieting, 1980-2010 (Box 72)
    - Food as Sex and Peace, 1985-1998 (Box 72)
    - Food as Love, 1996-1997 (Box 72)
    - Food, Diet, and Thinness, 1983-1998 (Box 72)
    - Greed and Consumption, 1998 (Box 72)
    - Milk, 1995-1997 (Box 72)
    - Relationships, 1970-1998 (Box 72)
    - Esquire Magazine, 1937 April (Box 73)
    - Foreign Ads-Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 73)
    - General Ads, 1978-1983 (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1983; 4 folders (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1998 (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1998 (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001-2009 (Box 73)
    - Old Ads, 1949-1951 (Box 73)
    - Subliminals, 1967-1981 (Box 73)
    - Subliminals: General, 1975-1985 (Box 73)
    - Values, Feelings, and Miscellaneous, 1991-1998 (Box 73)
  - Men and Miscellaneous Ads, 5
    - Ads: General, 1978-1980 (Box 74)
    - Cartoons, 1996-2008 (Box 74)
    - Life Magazine, 1967 (Box 74)
    - Little Boys, 1978-1983 (Box 74)
    - Men, 2000 and undated (Box 74)
    - Men: Nontraditional, 1979-1984 (Box 74)
    - Men: Sex Objects/Looks, 1977-1985 (Box 74)
    - Men: Success Objects, 1983-1985 (Box 74)
    - Men: Traditional, 1966-1985 (Box 74)
    - Medical Ads, 1979 (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-2001 (Box 74)
    - No Comment Ads, 1978-1983 (Box 74)
    - Political Advertising, 1992-1996 (Box 74)
    - Positive Ads, 1977-1985 (Box 74)
    - South African Ads, 2006-2007 (Box 74)
    - Stereotypes/Gratuitous Insults, 1969-1985 (Box 74)
    - TNT Ads, 1978-1989 (Box 74)
  - Research and Violence Ads, 6
    - Adolescents and Advertising, 1986-2011 (Box 75)
    - Addiction as a Relationship, 1978-1997 (Box 75)
    - Anti-Advertising/Cynicism, 1991-1998 (Box 75)
    - Anti-Drug Campaigns, 1989-1999 (Box 75)
    - Body Language, 1969-1981 (Box 75)
    - Research and Effects, 1997-1998 (Box 75)
    - Values, 1997-2008 (Box 75)
    - Values and Feelings, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
    - Violence: General and "Romantic" Stranger, 1985-2001 (Box 75)
    - Violence and Abuse: Bondage and Movie Ads, 1978-1985 (Box 75)
    - Violence and Abuse: Covert, 1975-1984 (Box 75)
    - Violence and Abuse: Overt, 1931-1984 (Box 75)
  - Sexuality and Beauty, 7
    - Artificiality/Cosmetics, 1969-1985 (Box 76)
    - Beauty, 1998-2011 (Box 76)
    - Beauty Myth, 1982-1995 (Box 76)
    - Fashions and Lingerie, 1976-1983 (Box 76)
    - Homosexuality, 1982-1985 (Box 76)
    - Sex Ads, 1992-2003 (Box 76)
    - Sexual Sell: Unrelated Products, 1964-1985 (Box 76)
    - Sexualization of Products, 1981-1984 (Box 76)
    - Teenagers: Sexuality, 1979-1983 (Box 76)
    - The Image (Femininity, etc.), 1977-1985 (Box 76)
  - Targeting and Marketing, 8
    - Advertising, 1999-2001 (Box 77)
    - Food Ads, 1986-2003 (Box 77)
    - Marketing Alcohol, 1980-1984 (Box 77)
    - Marketing Strategies, 1982-1985 (Box 77)
    - Marketing to Women, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
    - Minorities, 1976-1985 (Box 77)
    - Targeting-ALC and Drugs, 1980-1999 (Box 77)
    - Targeting Children and Youth, 1993-1998 (Box 77)
    - Targeting: The Internet, 1995-1998 (Box 77)
    - Targeting Men, 1990-1997 (Box 77)
    - Targeting Minorities, 1993-1998 (Box 77)
    - Targeting Miscellaneous, 1983-1998 (Box 77)
    - Targeting Women, 1977-1997 (Box 77)
  - Women, 9
    - Aging/Older Women, 1976-1984 (Box 78)
    - Gender: Sex and Violence, 2001-2009 (Box 78)
    - Girls 1, 1992-1998 (Box 78)
    - Girls 2, 1990-1998 (Box 78)
    - Hair, 1973-1985 (Box 78)
    - Heavier Models, 1983-1986 (Box 78)
    - Little Girls, 2005-2009 (Box 78)
    - Sexism, 1990-2011 (Box 78)
    - Skinny Models, 1996-1997 (Box 78)
    - Slim Models, 1980-1985 (Box 78)
    - Women, 1984-2004 (Box 78)
    - Breasts and Breastfeeding, 1994-1999 (Box 79)
    - Evil Women, 1968-1985 (Box 79)
    - Feminine Hygiene, 1979-1984 (Box 79)
    - Housewives and Mothers, 1977-1984 (Box 79)
    - Little Girls, 1989-1997 (Box 79)
    - Violence and Abuse: Woman as Victims, 1978-1985 (Box 79)
    - Women, 1979-1997; 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Women, 1989-2004 (Box 79)
    - Women, 1996-2001 (Box 79)
    - Women of Color and Ethnic Ads, 1988-2005 (Box 79)
  - Body and Career, 10
    - The Body, 2000-2003 (Box 80)
    - Body: Bust, 1975-1984 (Box 80)
    - Body: Bust--Maidenform, undated (Box 80)
    - The Body: Derriere, 1977-1981; 3 folders (Box 80)
    - The Body: Derriere, 1977-1981 (Box 80)
    - The Body: Derriere, 1978-1985 (Box 80)
    - Body: Dismemberment and Objectification, 1969-1984 (Box 80)
    - The Body: Legs, 1979-1984 (Box 80)
    - Careers and Work, 1976-1985 (Box 80)
    - Competition, 1977-1983 (Box 80)
    - Class, 1982-1985 (Box 80)
    - Food and Diet, 1997-2004 (Box 80)
  - Cigarettes, 11
    - Cigarette Ads, 1989-2003 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Benson and Hedges, 1974-1992 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Camel, 1984-1996 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Foreign Ads, 1991-1995 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Freedom/Independence, 1974-1996 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-In Other Ads ("Bad Girls"), 1991-1996 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Kool, 1987-1995 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Marlboro, 1972-1985 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Merit, 1979-1996 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-More, 1981-1988 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes (Old Ads), pre-1970 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Parliament, 1980-1996 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Rebellion, 1980-1996 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Risk Takers, 1973-1992 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Salem, 1989-1990 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Sexual Sell, 1973-1991 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Targeting Women (Miscellaneous), 1975-1993 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Violence/Death/Destruction, 1978-1994 (Box 81)
    - Cigarettes-Weight Control, 1980-1996 (Box 81)
    - Newport-Food, 1987-1992 (Box 81)
    - Newport-Miscellaneous, 1978-1992 (Box 81)
    - Newport-Violence, 1981-1996 (Box 81)
    - Subliminals-Cigarettes, 1976-1989 (Box 81)
    - Tobacco, 1989-1992 (Box 81)
    - Tobacco Ads, 2001-2003 (Box 81)
    - Tobacco Industry Ads-General, 1978-1996 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Slims, 1983-1998 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Slims-Miscellaneous, 1986-1995 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Slims-Phallic Symbols, 1984-1986 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Slims-Social Consciousness, 1992-1994 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Slims-Violence, 1976-1991 (Box 81)
    - Virginia-Slims-Weight Control, 1977-1991 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Slims-Women of Color, 1983-1989 (Box 81)
  - Cigarettes and Cars, 12
    - Car Ads, 1981-1997; 4 folders (Box 82)
    - Car Ads, 1990-1997 (Box 82)
    - Car Ads, 1994-2003 (Box 82)
    - Car Ads, 1996-1998 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Act and Creativity, 1981 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Boredom/Escape, 1984-1996 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Low Tap, Low Price, 1975-1996 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Luck of the Draw, 1987-1991 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Macho, 1975-1996 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Miscellaneous, 1989-1996 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Nature, 1977-1990 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-People of Color, 1986-1992 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Quitting, Negative Aspects, etc., 1990 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Sports, 1978-1989 (Box 82)
    - Cigarettes-Targeting Children, 1986-1995 (Box 82)
    - Smokeless-Tobacco, 1989-1995 (Box 82)
  - Cross-Cultural, 13
    - Cross-Cultural: Brazil, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Cross-Cultural: England, 1979-1981; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Cross-Cultural: France, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Cross-Cultural: Italy, 1979-1981; 3 folders (Box 83)
    - Cross-Cultural: Oriental (Japan and China), undated (Box 83)
  - Magazines, 14
    - Collier's Magazine, 1948 Sept.-Oct.; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Life Magazine, 1947 10 Feb. (Box 84)
    - Town and Country Magazine, 1948 Oct.; 4 folders (Box 84)
    - Vogue Magazine, 1951 Nov. 1 (Box 84)
  - Media and Medical Ads, 15
    - Ad Age Ads, 1981-1999 (Box 85)
    - Adv-Parodies, Cartoons, 1988-1998 (Box 85)
    - Advertising, 1999 (Box 85)
    - Coopting Revolution, 1988-1998 (Box 85)
    - Drugs, 1977-1981 (Box 85)
    - Medical Ads, 1957-1981; 3 folders (Box 85)
    - Medical Ads, 1963-1983 (Box 85)
    - Medical Ads, 1978-1979 (Box 85)
    - Resources for Change: Positive Images, 1981-1992 (Box 85)
    - Violence, 1988-1997 (Box 85)
  - Men and Women; Media Censorship, 16
    - Lesbians/Gay Men, 1990-1991 (Box 86)
    - Media Censorship, 1983-1997 (Box 86)
    - Men: Objectification and Control, 1988-1999 (Box 86)
    - Women, 1983-1995; 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Women, 1983-1996 (Box 86)
    - Women, 1987-1996 (Box 86)
  - Sexuality and Liberation, 17
    - Blatant Sexuality, 1986-1995 (Box 87)
    - Liberation: Careers and Work, 1974-1984 (Box 87)
    - Liberation: Coopting the Movement, 1970-1992 (Box 87)
    - Liberation: General, 1977-1985 (Box 87)
    - Liberation: Narcissism and Auto-Eroticism, 1978-1990 (Box 87)
    - Liberation: Sexual Freedom and Secret, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
    - Liberation: Superwoman, 1980-1984 (Box 87)
    - Pornography, 1980-1996 (Box 87)
    - Relationships: Things as Lovers and Lovers as Things, 1981-1998 (Box 87)
    - Values/Relationships, 1983-2003; 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Values/Relationships, 1995-1999 (Box 87)
  - The Naked Truth (TNT), 18
    - TNT 1, 1983-1986 (Box 88)
    - TNT 2, 1984-1986 (Box 88)
    - TNT 3, 1979-1988; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - TNT 4, 1986-1987 (Box 88)
    - TNT 5: Dieting and Body Image, 1987-1988 (Box 88)
    - TNT 6, 1978-1986 (Box 88)
    - TNT 7, 1973-1986 (Box 88)
    - TNT 8, 1980-1987; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - TNT 9, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 88)
- Printed Materials, 1933-2014; 1; 5 boxes
  - A Hunger So Wide and So Deep: A Multiracial View of Women's Eating Problems. Becky W. Thompson. University of Minnesota Press. English., 1994 (Box PM1)
  - Afraid to Eat: Children and Teens in Weight Crisis. Frances M. Berg. Healthy Weight Journal. English., 1997 (Box PM1)
  - All Made Up: A Girl's Guide to Seeing Through Celebrity Hype--and Celebrating Real Beauty. Audrey Brashich. Walker Publishing Company. English., 2006 (Box PM1)
  - Almost Anorexic: Is My (or My Loved One's) Relationship with Food a Problem? Jennifer J. Thomas, PhD and Jenni Schaefer. Harvard Health Publications. English., 2013 (Box PM1)
  - Bullied: What Every Parent, Teacher and Kid Needs to Know About Ending the Cycle of Fear. Carrie Coldman. HarperCollins. English., 2012 (Box PM1)
  - Can't Buy My Love: How Advertising Changes the Way we Think and Feel. Jean Kilbourne. Touchstone. English., 1999 (Box PM1)
  - Can't Buy My Love: How Advertising Changes the Way we Think and Feel. Jean Kilbourne. Owl Publishing House. Japanese., 2001 (Box PM1)
  - Can't Buy My Love: How Advertising Changes the Way we Think and Feel. Jean Kilbourne. Owl Publishing House. Japanese., 2001 (Box PM1)
  - Can't Buy My Love: How Advertising Changes the Way we Think and Feel. Jean Kilbourne. Owl Publishing House. Japanese., 2001 (Box PM1)
  - Chemical Dependency: Women at Risk. Brenda L. Underhill and Dana G. Finnegan-Editors. Harrington Park Press. English., 1996 (Box PM1)
  - Children, Adolescents, and the Media. Victor C. Strasburger and Barbara J. Wilson. SAGE Publications. English., 2002 (Box PM1)
  - Children, Adolescents, and the Media. Victor C. Strasburger, Barbara J. Wilson and Amy B. Jordan. SAGE Publications. English., 2009 (Box PM1)
  - Deadly Persuasion: Why Women and Girls Must Fight the Addictive Power of Advertising. Jean Kilbourne. Owl Publishing House. Japanese., 2001 (Box PM1)
  - Deadly Persuasion: Why Women and Girls Must Fight the Addictive Power of Advertising. Jean Kilbourne. Owl Publishing House. Japanese., 2001 (Box PM1)
  - Deadly Persuasion: Why Women and Girls Must Fight the Addictive Power of Advertising. Jean Kilbourne. The Free Press. English., 1999 (Box PM1)
  - Feminism and Addiction. Claudia Bepko- Editor. Haworth Press. English., 1991 (Box PM1)
  - Gender Advertisements. Erving Goffman. Harper and Row Publishers. English., 1976 (Box PM1)
  - God and Boobs: Balancing Faith and Sexuality. Angie Schuller Wyatt. Angie Schuller Wyatt. English., 2012 (Box PM1)
  - Her Next Chapter: How Mother-Daughter Book Clubs Can Help Girls Navigate Malicious Media, Risky Relationships, Girl Gossip, and so Much More. Lori Day, M.Ed. With Charlotte Kulger. Chicago Review Press. English., 2014 (Box PM1)
  - If the Buddha had Kids: Raising Children to Create a More Peaceful World. Charlotte Kasl, Ph.D. Penguin Books. English., 2012 (Box PM1)
  - In Your Face: The Culture of Beauty and You. Shari Graydon. Annick Press. English., 2004 (Box PM1)
  - Life Without Ed: How One Woman Declared Independence from Her Eating Disorder and How You Can Too. Jenni Schaefer. McGraw Hill. English., 2004 (Box PM1)
  - Low-Fat Love. Patricia Leavy. Sense Publications. English., 2011 (Box PM1)
  - Mother Power: Discover the Difference That Women Have Made All Over the World. Jacqueline Hornor Plumez. Ph.D. SourceBooks. English., 2002 (Box PM1)
  - Pedagogy of the Oppressed. Paulo Freire. The Seabury Press. English., 1970 (Box PM1)
  - Red Boots and Attitude: The Spirit of Texas Women Writers. Diane Fanning and Susie Kelly Flatau. Eaking Press. English., 2002 (Box PM1)
  - Redefining Girly: How Parents can Fight the Stereotyping and Sexualizing of Girlhood, from Birth to Tween. Melissa Atkins Wardy. Chicago Review Press. English., 2014 (Box PM1)
  - So Sexy so Soon: The New Sensualized Childhood and What Parents Can do to Protect Their Kids. Diane E. Levin and Jean Kilbourne. Ballantine Books. Russian., 2008 (Box PM1)
  - The Gift of Change: Spiritual Guidance for Living Your Best Life. Marianne Williamson. HarperCollins. English., 2004 (Box PM1)
  - The Healing Connection: How Women Form Relationships in Therapy and in Life. Jean Baker Miller, M.D. and Irene Pierce Stiver, Ph.D. Beacon Press. English., 1997 (Box PM1)
  - The Price of Privilege: How Parental Pressure and Material Advantage are Creating a Generation of Disconnected and Unhappy Kids. Madeline Levine, Ph.D. HarperCollins. English., 2006 (Box PM1)
  - The Ultimate Tween Survival Guide. Eating Disorder: Understanding Them, Preventing Tem and Helping a Loved One. Dina Zeckhauses, PhD. Book Logix. English., 2012 (Box PM1)
  - Where the Girls are: Growing up Female with the Mass Media. Susan J. Douglas. Times Books. English., 1994 (Box PM1)
  - Women and Aging: Celebrating Ourselves. Ruth Raymond Thone. Harrington Park Press. English., 1992 (Box PM1)
  - Your Dieting Daughter: Antidotes Parents can Provide for Body Dissatisfaction, excessive Dieting, and Disordered Eating. Carolyn Costin. Routledge. English., 2013 (Box PM1)
  - Modern Man in Search of a Soul. C. G. Jung. Harvest Publishers. English., 1933 (Box PM2)
  - A General Theory of Love. Thomas Lewis, M.D., Fari Amini, M.D., Richard Lannon, M.D. Vintage Books. English., 2000 (Box PM2)
  - Adios, Barbie: Young Women Write About Body Image and Identity. Edited by Ophira Edut. Seal Press. English., 1998 (Box PM2)
  - Altered Loves: Mothers and Daughters During Adolescence. Terri Apter. Ballantine Books. English., 1990 (Box PM2)
  - Autobiography of a Face. Lucy Grealy. Houghton Mifflin Company. English., 1994 (Box PM2)
  - Breaking Down the Wall of Silence: The Liberating Experience of Facing Painful Truth. Alice Miller (Translator). Dutton Books. English., 1991 (Box PM2)
  - Captains of Consciousness: Advertising and the Social Roots of the Consumer Culture. Stuart Ewen. McGraw Hill Book Company. English., 1976 (Box PM2)
  - Carjacked: The Culture of the Automobile and its Effect on Our lives. Catherine Lutz and Anne Lutz Fernandez. Palgrave McMillan. English., 2010 (Box PM2)
  - Cosmetics, Fashions, and the Exploitation of Women. Joseph Hansen and Evelyn Reed. Pathfinder Press. English., 1986 (Box PM2)
  - Decoding Advertisements: Ideology and Meaning in Advertising. Judith Williamson. Marion Boyars Publishing. English., 1978 (Box PM2)
  - Getting to Yes: Negotiating Agreement Without Giving In. Roger Fisher and William Ury. Penguin Books. English., 1981 (Box PM2)
  - Illness as Metaphor. Susan Sontag. Farrar, Straus and Giroux. English., 1977 (Box PM2)
  - Juicy Tomatoes: Plain Truths, Dumb Lies, and Sisterly Advice About Life After 50. Susan Swartz. Publishers Group West. English., 2000 (Box PM2)
  - Man and His Symbols. Carl G. Jung, M.-L. Franz, Joseph L. Henderson, Jolande Jacobi and Aniela Jaffe. Dell Publishing Co. English., 1964 (Box PM2)
  - Memories, Dreams, Reflections. C. G. Jung. Vintage Books. English., 1965 (Box PM2)
  - Mother Daughter Revolution: From Good Girls to Great Women. Elizabeth Debold, Marie Wilson, Idelisse Malave. Bantam Books. English., 1993 (Box PM2)
  - Neurotic Styles. David Shapiro. Basic Books, Inc. English., 1965 (Box PM2)
  - On Lies, Secrets, and Silence. Adrienne Rich. W. W. and Company. English., 1979 (Box PM2)
  - On Photography. Susan Sontag. Farrar, Straus and Giroux. English., 1973 (Box PM2)
  - Pornography and Silence: Culture's Revenge Against Nature. Susan Griffin. Harper and Row Publishers. English., 1981 (Box PM2)
  - Putting on Appearances: Gender and Advertising. Diane Barthel. Temple University Press. English., 1988 (Box PM2)
  - Reviving Ophelia: Saving the Selves of Adolescent Girls. Mary Pipher, Ph.D. Ballantine Books. English., 1994 (Box PM2)
  - Sex: Stereotyping in Advertising. Alice E. Courtney, Thomas W. Whipple. Lexington Books. English., 1983 (Box PM2)
  - Steps to an Ecology of Mind: A Revolutionary Approach to Man's Understanding of Himself. Gregory Bateson. Chandler Publishing Company. English., 1972 (Box PM2)
  - Teaching as a Subversive Activity. Neil Postman and Charles Weingartner. Delacorte Press. English., 1969 (Box PM2)
  - The Courage to Create. Rollo May. Bantam Books. English., 1975 (Box PM2)
  - The Courage to Write: How Writer's Transcend Fear. Ralph Keyes. Henry Holt and Company. English., 1995 (Box PM2)
  - The Duke of Deception: A Son's Extraordinary Story of a Bad Man and a Good Father. Geoffrey Wolff. Berkley Books. English., 1979 (Box PM2)
  - The Garden of Eating: Food, Sex, and the Hunger for Meaning. Jeremy Iggers. Basic Books. English., 1996 (Box PM2)
  - The Hidden Persuaders. Vance Packard. Pocket Books Inc. English., 1957 (Box PM2)
  - UConn Huskies Men's Basketball. Wayne Norman and Robert Porter. Globe Pequot Press. English., 2005 (Box PM2)
  - Values Clarification: A Handbook of Practical Strategies for Teachers and Students. Sidney B. Simon, Leland W. Howe, Howard Kirschenbaum. Hart Publishing Company, Inc. English., 1972 (Box PM2)
  - Women, Sex, and Addiction: A Search for Love and Power. Charlotte Davis Kasl, Ph.D. Ticknor and Fields. English., 1989 (Box PM2)
  - Working it Out: 23 Women Writers, Artists, Scientists, and Scholars Talk About Their Lives and Work. Edited by Sara Ruddick and Pamela Daniels. Pantheon Books. English., 1977 (Box PM2)